# **Bradan Schwanke**Software Engineer

Innovative software engineer with professional experience in full-stack development for growing business. Highly knowledgeable in an array of languages, frameworks, and tools for web and mobile development to deliver helpful, effective, and visually pleasing applications.

# **Work Experience**

### Firmware Engineer at Control by Web

Developed embedded webpages for PLCs which implemented MQTT using Bootstrap and C. Wrote back-end software using the Laravel framework for communication between front-end interfaces and multiple cellular service APIs.

July 2023 - Current

## Technical Support Agent at EFORCE Software

Addressed bugs presented by clients concerning the browser-based software. Used SQL to write queries to locate corrupt data in the client's database and perform commands to resolve the issue. Kept workload organized using Jira.

Feb 2022 - Sept 2022

## Electrical Engineer Intern at iFIT Health & Fitness

Wrote embedded software and did testing for iFIT's fitness products. Main focus was using BLE and capacitive sensors to record and analyze data for runners.

May 2021 - Sept 2021

## **Education**

Bachelor's of Science in Electrical Engineering Minor in Computer Science

Utah State University Logan, Utah 2017-2022

### Contact

801-800-2444 bradanschwanke.work@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/bradanschwanke github.com/braysch

Logan, Utah

# **Expertise**

Programming	(7y)
Mobile Development	(3y)
Web Development	(3y)
UI Design	(3y)
Back-end Development	(3y)
API Integration	(1y)
Embedded Systems	(4y)
Database Management	(2 <sub>V</sub> )

# Skills

React	(1y)
JavaScript	(3y)
TypeScript	(1y)
HTML	(3y)
CSS	(3y)
Tailwind	(1y)
PHP	(1y)
Laravel	(1y)
SQL	(2y)
Bootstrap	(1y)
Python	(2y)
Visual Studio	(5y)

Self-motivation Critical Thinking Teamwork Flexibility Communication Problem-solving